{
    "id": "71512d3dc76d4b7291242617732f79dd",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………. are useful devices.",
            "description": "We do not use ‘the’ with plural nouns to talk about things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "Computers",
                "The computers",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6fbfa9c562845ef8ca9d12026da95a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I love …………………",
            "description": "We do not use ‘the’ with plural nouns to talk about things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "mushrooms",
                "the mushrooms",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96d6b536fae64affb74d65c79730a67c"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. birds can fly.",
            "description": "When most means ‘the majority of’, it is used without the.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2535115d58144b3a9ab416870d08cd80"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mother is in ……………… She has kidney trouble.",
            "description": "We use 'the' with hospital only when the reference is to the building. ",
            "answers": [
                "hospital",
                "the hospital",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "80065ba918de4b66bd17b6d0ccfebbd2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Both …………….. are good at painting.",
            "description": "We often leave out ‘the’ after both.",
            "answers": [
                "children",
                "the children",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c863fc6f63ed45af99d06ad1449c1d27"
        },
        {
            "question": "All ……………… robbers have been arrested.",
            "description": "We often leave out ‘the’ between all and a number.",
            "answers": [
                "five",
                "the five",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0a5108beacf645798544b162e80e9341"
        },
        {
            "question": "The number of …………….. has increased rapidly.",
            "description": "‘The’ is dropped after ‘the number of’ or ‘the amount of’.",
            "answers": [
                "unemployed",
                "the unemployed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2846e78896b74e71a6bc14182f147c9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is that on ……………….?",
            "description": "The article ‘the’ is common with the names of musical instruments.",
            "answers": [
                "piano",
                "the piano",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8b78f310b79d4aa983afb25af65a2ab1"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is not easy to produce programs for …………….",
            "description": "Articles are generally used with radio, cinema and theater.",
            "answers": [
                "radio",
                "the radio",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "838c9e4072ec485cb4f02a3290437198"
        },
        {
            "question": "What …………….. idea!",
            "description": "We use’a/an’ with singular countable nouns in exclamations after what.",
            "answers": [
                "brilliant",
                "a brilliant",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "72e69c9b02554888b3756f654c7af811"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you get that cat off …………….?",
            "description": "Articles are used with TV when the reference is to a television set.",
            "answers": [
                "TV",
                "the TV",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "195c5ca174e44b54a3946c483fed8355"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am getting ……………",
            "description": "'A toothache' is more common in American English. ",
            "answers": [
                "toothache",
                "a toothache",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "221359ae105e4212ae7a2f9a1f4f3e25"
        }
    ]
}